arctic-cooling.com 2012-11-18

# Privacy Policy · Arctic Cooling

**Information Collection and Use**  

ARCTIC COOLING is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you select to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items.

**Registration**

In order to process your orders placed on our webshop, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important ARCTIC COOLING services such as automated order status updates via e-mail.

**Order**

The information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide your credit card number, expiry date, mailing address, contact telephone number etc. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except the merchant bank mentioned above. No financial information such as your credit card number will be stored and used after the completion of your order.

**Cookies**

We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our Webshop but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The ARCTIC COOLING shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, ARCTIC COOLING will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [ARCTIC COOLING](http://www.arctic-cooling.com/) only.

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

**Sharing**

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

_Hong Kong Post Office  
Headquarters_  
2 Connaught Place,  
Central,   
Hong Kong

| 

_MoneyBookers  
Headquarters_  
Welken House  
10-11 Charterhouse Square  
London EC1M 6EH  
United States

| 

 _United Parcel Services  
Corporate Headquarters_  
55 Glenlake Parkway, NE  
Atlanta , GA  30328   
United States

---|---|---  
  
We may frame or mask another web site so that the look, feel and interface simulate the experience of browsing a genuine ARCTIC COOLING web page. Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.   

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that ARCTIC COOLING is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Webshop.

**Security**  

ARCTIC COOLING takes precautions to protect its customers‘ Information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the encryption software currently available in the industry – SSL. ARCTIC COOLING uses the most advanced form of SSL software available: 256-bit encryption by thawte. To learn more about SSL, follow this link www.geotrust.com. Access to all of our users‘ information is restricted. Your financial information such as credit card number will not be stored after the completion of orders.

All ARCTIC COOLING servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by multiple firewalls and password protection. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked area. All backups are stored and locked in a high-level security area. Only personnel with proper security clearance have access to these restricted areas. Backups are not permitted to leave the premises without prior authorization.  

If you have any questions or concerns about ARCTIC COOLING‘s security practices, please email us at [info@arctic-cooling.com.](mailto:info@arctic-cooling.com)

### Newsletter

Our Newsletter is sent only to customers who grant ARCTIC COOLING permission to send them such information.   

To honor the privacy of our users, we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. At the time of your registration, you may opt to not receive newsletter by clicking the appropriate field. Furthermore, all newsletter are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive it in the future. Please reference the Opt-out section below for further details on how to be removed from our mailing list.

**View and update Personal Information**

Customers may change or review their stored account information such as address book or contact number through our website by logging in to My Account section. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact us at [eshop@arctic-cooling.com.](mailto:eshop@arctic-cooling.com)

**Opt-out**

For customers who wish to opt-out and stop receiving ARCTIC COOLING Newsletter, users may uncheck the appropriate box in your Account information or send e-mail to newsletter@arctic-cooling.com with "unsubscribe" in subject line and your User ID of the Webshop. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

**Last Update**

The Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective from 1 August 2009
